粵文字幕 www.cantocaptions.com
Cantonese Subtitles www.cantocaptions.com
媽媽
Mom
爸爸
Dad
巴高
Bingo
保怡
Bluey
媽媽				我唔係你媽媽
Mom				I'm not your mom
我意思係爸爸
I mean Dad
係
Yes
我哋而家可以玩伏匿匿未啊？
Can we play hide-and-seek now?
等多陣吖
Wait a moment
點解嗰隻狗石像淨係坐喺度𠸏？
Why is that stone dog statue just sitting there?
佢喺度練習緊唔好被分散注意力啊
He's practicing not getting distracted.
咩話？呢啲噉嘅嘢唔使練習囖
What? You don't need to practice something like that.
你真係肯定？
Are you really sure?
係啊
Yes.
唔被分散注意力好易吒嗎，睇下
It's easy not to get distracted, watch.
噢，係隻蜻蜓啊！
Oh, it's a dragonfly!
紅蘿蔔角
Carrot sticks.
喂，巴高，我哋玩伏匿匿吖
Hey, Bingo, let's play hide-and-seek.
好啊，玩伏匿匿
Okay, let's play hide-and-seek!
今次保怡嘅故事係關於
This Bluey story is about
［伏匿匿］
[Hide-and-Seek]
好喇，你哋匿埋
Okay, you guys hide.
我就去捉你哋，開始！
I'm going to catch you, start!
一、二…
One, two...
等一陣先
Wait a moment.
係啊，等一陣先啊				等一陣啊
Yeah, wait a moment.				Wait a moment.
要我哋匿埋嘅話
If you want us to hide,
你就要保證你唔可以玩玩下
Then you have to promise to not just play a little
走咗去揾石頭㗎喎
and then go play with rocks.
我從來都唔會噉做𠸏
I would never do that.
會啊，你試過喇				會啊，你試過喇
Yes, you have!				Yes, you have!
好啦…我保證
Okay... I promise.
好				好
Okay.				Okay.
而家去啦
Start now!
一、二、三…				耶！
One, two, three...				Yay!
哎吔，巴高，佢數緊喇
Oh no, Bingo, she's counting!
快啲啦，我哋要匿埋啊
Hurry up, we need to hide!
六、七、八…
Six, seven, eight...
唔好被分散注意力吖
Don't get distracted!
十、十一、十二…
Ten, eleven, twelve...
十三、十四、十五…
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen...
十六、十七…
Sixteen, seventeen...
十八、十九、二十！
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
得未啊？我嚟捉你哋喇！
Are you ready yet? I'm coming to get you!
好，諗下佢哋可能匿喺邊先
Okay, let's think about where they might be hiding first.
噢，係網球
Oh, it's a tennis ball.
噢，唔可以分散注意力啊，保怡
Oh, can't get distracted, Bluey.
呢度都冇喎
They're not here either.
佢哋真係匿得好好啊
They're really hiding well.
有冇邊個喺度啊？
Is anyone here?
吱喳仔！
Ji-Ja-Jai!
我仲以為我唔見咗你啊
I thought I had lost you.
你肚餓呀，吱喳仔？
Are you hungry, Ji-Ja-Jai?
餵我！
Feed me!
我都想餵你，但係…
I want to feed you, but...
我而家應該要玩伏匿匿㗎
I'm supposed to be playing hide-and-seek right now.
好啦，我快快手餵你食少少嘢啦
Okay, I'll quickly feed you a little something.
我都唔明點解你會去咗鋅盤櫃入面㗎
I don't understand why you went inside the sink cabinet.
餵我
Feed me!
好啦，你想食嗰啲嘢擺喺邊呢？
Okay, where's the stuff you like to eat?
吱喳仔，我知喇，咪揾緊囖
Ji-Ja-Jai, I know, I'm looking for it.
揾到喇！
Found it!
吱喳糖
Ji-Ja candy!
嗱，你嘅
Here, for you.
好味…
Delicious...
好喇，我要返去繼續捉佢哋喇
Alright, I need to go back to catching them.
廁所…
Bathroom...
噢，吱喳仔
Oh, Ji-Ja-Jai.
便便…
Poo-poo...
嗱，去啦，辦你嘅大事啦
Okay, go on, do your business.
噢，好啦，吱喳仔
Alright, Ji-Ja-Jai.
我要失陪先啊
I must excuse myself.
好啦，我頭先做緊咩㗎呢？
Okay, what was I doing just now?
去完廁所…
Finished toilet…
吱喳仔應該要我幫佢洗手啊
Ji-Ja-Jai probably needs help washing his hands.
點解呢度會咁污糟㗎？
Why is it so dirty here?
係𠸏，真係好有趣啊
Yes, very interesting.
洗…
Wash…
搞掂喇，吱喳仔，冇細菌喇
All done, Ji-Ja-Jai, no more germs.
好
Okay.
我而家要返返去…
I have to go back to...
我唔記得咗我要做咩喇
I forgot what I was supposed to do!
噢，好啦
Oh, alright then.
我諗我都係同你玩算喇
I think I'll just play with you.
再同你見面嘅感覺真係好啊，波莉
It feels so good to see you again, Polly.
你一定要講晒喇
You have to tell me everything.
去埃及旅行嘅嘢畀我聽啊
Tell me about your trip to Egypt.
好啊，好好玩㗎
Okay, it was so much fun!
你杯茶使唔使加啲奶啊？
Do you need some milk in your tea?
要啊，唔該
Yes, please.
你嘅，波莉
Yours, Polly.
噉你又要唔要啊，謝露？
Do you want any, Shirley?
吱喳仔
Ji-Ja-Jai!
呢個係茶會啊，唔係舞會嚟㗎
This is a tea party, not a dance party!
唔該唔好咁嘈啦！
Please don't be so loud!
我先生咁失禮，真係唔好意思啊
I'm so sorry that my husband is being so rude.
停啊，唔好啊！
Stop, don't!
佢成日都係噉㗎
He's always like this.
對唔住喇，吱喳仔
I'm sorry, Ji-Ja-Jai.
好明顯我哋唔可以噉樣一齊玩啊
It's obvious we can't play together like this.
我都係熄咗你一陣先啊
I'm just going to turn you off for a little bit.
點解你冇掣㗎？
Why don't you have a switch?
媽媽，幫我攞咗吱喳仔入面嘅電芯啊！
Mom, help me take out Ji-Ja-Jai's batteries!
靜啲啦，吱喳仔
Be quiet, Ji-Ja-Jai.
媽媽！
Mom!
你喺邊啊？
Where are you?
爸爸！
Dad!
巴高！巴高！
Bingo! Bingo!
點解一個二個都唔應我㗎？
Why isn't anyone answering me?
吱喳仔，你夠喇
Ji-Ja-Jai, that's enough.
佢哋全部去晒邊啊？
Where have they all gone?
好啦，我真係要靜一靜諗清楚
Okay, I really need some peace and quiet to think this through.
一、二、三、四
One, two, three, four.
噢，係喎，我記得喇
Oh, that's right, I remember now.
揾到！				好嘢！
Found you!				Nice!
揾到！
Found you!
真係吖
For real...
樖聖誕樹全程都喺我後邊㧻住我背脊啊
The Christmas tree was poking my back the whole time!
你哋信唔信啊？
Can you guys believe it?
我分散咗注意力
I got distracted.
竟然唔記得咗我哋玩緊伏匿匿
I actually forgot we were playing hide-and-seek.
信啊				信啊
We believe it.				We believe it.
真係似足你嘅作風啊
That's so typical of you.
而家你哋匿埋，我捉你哋啊
Now you guys hide, I'm going to catch you!
好吖				好啊
Okay!				Okay!
一、二、三、四…
One, two, three, four...
快啊，要快啲匿埋喇
Hurry, hide quickly!
巴高淨係識數到14㗎咋
Bingo only knows how to count to 14.
噢，蜻蜓喎
Oh, a dragonfly!
快啲行啦！				十、十一、十二…
Hurry up and walk!				Ten, eleven, twelve…
十三、十四…
Thirteen, fourteen…
得未啊？我嚟捉你哋喇！
Ready yet? I'm coming to catch you!
佢哋可以去咗邊度呢？
Where could they have gone?
佢哋可能匿咗喺…
They might be hiding in…
垃圾桶！
The trash can!
唔喺度喎
They're not here.
係喎，保怡
That's right, Bluey.
你點樣處置吱喳仔啊？
What did you do with the Ji-Ja-Jai?
噢，唔使擔心
Oh, don't worry.
我放咗佢喺一個好和平嘅地方
I put him in a very peaceful place.
佢哋可能匿埋咗喺…
They might be hiding in...
呢度，揾到喇！
Here, found them!
粵文字幕 www.cantocaptions.com
Cantonese Subtitles www.cantocaptions.com